

ABOUT ME

I am a Developer and Designer based in Hannover with a background in Hospitality and Sales.

As a Ironhack graduate I'm passionate about the design and the visual outcome of a product. Furthermore, I always aim to make the experience of a product a positive and intuitive one.

SKILLS

Web Development

- Frontend with CSS, HTML, JavaScript and React
- Backend with NodeJS, ExpressJS, Axios and Restful API
- Databases with MongoDB and Mongoose
- Version Control with Git and GitHub

Design

- UI Development and Design with Material UI, Materialize and Bootstrap
- Wireframing with Figma and Mockflow
- Prototyping with Figma
- Responsive Web Design
- Branding
- Style Guides & Pattern Library
- · Survey and Interview

LANGUAGES

German

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Portuguese

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Enalish

Professional Proficiency

Spanish

Elementary Proficiency

BERNARDO FONSECA TORRES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER | UX/UI DESIGNER BERNARDOFONSECA.NETLIFY.APP

PROJECTS

Kronos - Hotel Task Management System

- Web application built with NodeJS, ExpressJS, Bootstrap, Handlebars, HTML and CSS
 Devs guild E-Commerce
- Web application built with ReactJS, CommerceJS, Material UI, Stripe, CSS and HTML

Agoge - Learning Portal

 Web application built with ReactJS, Cloudinary, Bootstrap, NodeJS, ExpressJS, CSS and HTML

The Legend of N'Wah

• Simple game built with JavaScript, DOM manipulation, Canvas, CSS and HTML

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer @Lohoff

October 2021 - present

Frontend Developer | UX/UI Designer @Freelance

May 2021 - October 2021

Bartender @Freelance

August 2014 - November 2020

Sales Advisor @Massimo Dutti

October 2019 - October 2020 (Store closedown)

Bilingual Administrative Assistant @SprachOase

April 2017 - April 2018

Sales Advisor @Hennes & Mauritz

September 2014 - July 2018

Hotel Industry Expert | Trainee @Accor

September 2011 - July 2014

EDUCATION

Web Development Bootcamp | Tech School @Ironhack

Fullstack Development Campus focused on MERN Stack Development, Component and Object-oriented programming.

March 2021 - May 2021

Hotel Industry Expert | Apprenticeship @Accor

Hospitality Traineeship at Mercure Hotels focused on Front Office, Foods & Beverage, Event Management, Housekeeping and Sales.

September 2011 - July 2014

COURSES

UX|UI and Web Design Course @The Udemy Portal

Master Mobile and Web Design, User Interface + User Experience (UI/UX Design), HTML, and CSS by Andrei Neagoie and Daniel Schifano

July 2021

React Native Course @The Udemy Portal

React Native - The Practical Guide [2021 Edition] by Academind

by Maximilian Schwarzmüller

September 2021



